Guide to the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Audio Collection ALBA.AUDIO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Music, 1976-2002
  This series contains audio recordings of music, both commercial releases and home recordings by veterans and others. Materials date from 1976 to 2002. Some of the recordings are copies of other recordings, primarily records. The series contains a home recording by Max Parker, of his memories of being a prisoner of war in Spain, which combines narration with song, possibly a preliminary recording for or an unedited version of material he eventually released on a commercial recording.
  - "España, Vol. 1" (Commercial Release), 1976 (Box 5, Cassette 1-162)
  - "España Vol. 2" (Commercial Release), 1976 (Box 5, Cassette 1-163)
  - "La Internacional" (Commercial Release), 1977 (Box 5, Cassette 1-164)
  - "Last American Heroes," by Harry Fisher's Son (original composition; home recording), undated (Box 5, Cassette 1-165)
  - "Ride On," Christy Moore (Commercial Release), 1987 (Box 5, Cassette 1-166)
  - "Songs of the Spanish Civil War, Vol. #1 and Vol. #2" [tape copy of a Folkways recording], undated (Box 5, Cassette 1-167)
  - "We Had All the Good Songs," by Ross Altman (original composition; home recording), August 1987 (Box 5, Cassette 1-168)
  - [International Brigade Songs] (copy of another recording), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-169)
  - [Six Songs for Democracy Dixos de las Brigadas Internacionales] (tape copy of a record), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-170)
  - [Songs for Democracy] (tape copy of a record), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-171)
  - [Songs of the Lincoln Brigade] and "ILGWU - We Work, We Sing" (tape copy of a record), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-172)
  - [Spanish Civil War Songs] (tape copy of a record), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-173)
  - German and Italian Songs from the SCW (tape copy of a record; made by Tom Sarbaugh), February 2002 (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-174)
  - Trip to Spain: Singing [Spanish and English] (Recorded by Blythe Allison Bennett), October 1986 (Box Shared Tamiment 089, Cassette 1-175)